<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>PocketHost</title>
	<subtitle>Get a PocketBase backend for your next app in under 10 seconds.</subtitle>
	<link href="https://pockethost.io/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://pockethost.io/"/>
	<updated>2023-10-11T11:25:17Z</updated>
	<id>https://pockethost.io</id>
	<author>
		<name></name>
		<email></email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Version 0.9.3 Update</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.3/"/>
		<updated>2023-10-11T11:25:17Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.3/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pockethost.io&quot;&gt;PocketHost&lt;/a&gt;, the zero-config PocketBase hosting platform, has reached version 0.9.3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this v0.9.3 patch of PocketHost, we&#39;ve infused several enhancements, including refined release prompts and the incorporation of the &#39;rizzdown&#39; dependency. The previously included Light Theme Toggle in the dashboard was removed, unnecessary coding was pruned for streamlined performance, and error messages are now more detailed—providing better insights during Docker launch and unexpected PocketBase service exits. We&#39;ve also updated the &#39;.env&#39; template and revamped our writing style for release blog posts, polishing the user experience further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change Log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.3/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version 0.9.3 (patch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: enhancements for release prompts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: add rizzdown dependency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merge branch &#39;master&#39; of github.com:pockethost/pockethost&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dashboard - Removed Light Theme Toggle (#317)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove unnecessary env prefix from yarn dev&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: update .env template to use project root instead of pwd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: improved docker launch error messages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: pid now properly shows in debugging output&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: removed unnecessary subdomain check for mothership middleware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: fixed error message when pocketbase serve exits unexpectedly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: rizz package name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: update proompts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: release blog post template&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: update the writing style for release blog posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: 0.9.2 frontmatter yaml syntax fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: 0.9.2 release doc formatting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.9.2: Unleashing Enhanced Security &amp; Streamlined Experience</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.2/"/>
		<updated>2023-10-06T04:22:08Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hot off the digital press, welcome to the upgraded version of PocketHost, v0.9.2! Like an episode of &#39;Silicon Valley&#39; meets &#39;Mr. Robot,&#39; this upgraded experience is reliable, intuitive, and smoother than butter on a hot knife. We&#39;ve been beavering away behind the scenes, embracing the profound power of &lt;code&gt;rizzdown&lt;/code&gt; to AI-enhance our docs and blogs. Just as Neo sees the Matrix, our content is now rizz&#39;d, bringing you clarity amidst complexity, conveniently affixed with community discussion links.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve fixed and finessed to enhance your user experience. With bug-bashing efforts on linting errors using prettier, we&#39;ve added JSON file types to linting, smoothed over registration processes and GitHub Actions, and even added &lt;code&gt;patch-package&lt;/code&gt; post-processing to all monorepo packages. Imagine the power of Mjolnir in web development, literally raining down patches in all the right places.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our latest dashboard is a work of art, fully supporting a full-screen logging view for instances. It wears a new suit, tailored in the DaisyUI and Tailwind framework, adding a razzle-dazzle element to your working experience. We turned the protective dial up to &#39;John Wick&#39; levels by introducing IPCIDR filtering – now all traffic must go through the Cloudflare proxy for comprehensive DDos and security coverage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest game-changer is the simplified proxy layers from the PocketHost daemon, enhancing reliability to match the highest level of coder zen that comes from less code. With OpenGraph metadata enhancements and a &lt;code&gt;return to top&lt;/code&gt; button, we&#39;ve summoned Avenger-like levels of user-experience power. Try out the new features and immerse yourself in a strengthened, simplified, and slicker PocketHost world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change Log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version 0.9.2 (patch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed Github Actions to properly publish the www static site when commits to the master branch are made&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Started using &lt;code&gt;rizzdown&lt;/code&gt; to generate AI-enhanced docs and blog posts. All content has been updated with rizz&#39;d versions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added community discussion links to the bottom of all blog posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed linting errors using prettier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added JSON file types to linting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;code&gt;patch-package&lt;/code&gt; postprocessing to all monorepo packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: github actions memo output formatting on master&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: github actions to only notify Discord if files have actually changed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added LICENSE.md and small edits in readme.md (#312)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed all references to the old gitbook documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dashboard - Sidebar Maintenance &amp;amp; Confirm Account Banner (#310)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dashboard now supports full screen logging view for instances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a &lt;code&gt;return to top&lt;/code&gt; button on all blog and documentation pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug preventing registration and signup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added OpenGraph metadata enhancements to all blog and documentation pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deployed a new dashboard using the DaisyUI and Tailwind frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;code&gt;prettier&lt;/code&gt; hooks on build steps in &lt;code&gt;husky&lt;/code&gt; hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added IPCIDR filtering. Now all traffic must go through the Cloudflare proxy. The origin will reject it otherwise. This is important for DDoS and other security measures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed the top-level proxy from the PocketHost daemon, thus simplifying the number of layers involved in proxying traffic to instances. Fewer layers and less code means more reliability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the PocketBase JS SDK to the latest version&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encapsulated HTTP/HTTPS into a variable for an easier developer experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed CORS headers in realtime logging code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed documentation links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.9.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.1/"/>
		<updated>2023-10-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gear up and venture forth into the labyrinth of coding realms with PocketHost 0.9.1. No need to pack your own provisions. This zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform caters to your every software-dev whim like a Gandalf-grade wizard; all magic, no tricks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a deep breath and plunge into a maintenance release that sets new standards with mind-blowing enhancements. Crisp, clear documentation is like the &#39;Alexandria Library&#39; for developers, letting you absorb knowledge as effortlessly as Neo in the Matrix. Code refactoring, continuous integration, and glistening Github actions are the invisible threads that weave the fabric of a well-optimized and seamless dev journey. Don&#39;t forget the garnish; the pièce de résistance is the enhanced proxy error trapping, alerting you like Spidey Senses on Red Bull.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unpack a treasure trove of changes in the latest changelog. From hoisting micro-dash, typefest and chalk, to our own PocketHost JS SDK, and a prettier-update, it&#39;s like discovering alien tech in your backyard. We&#39;ve dealt with bugs like Thor deals with misbehaving minions, squashed and silenced for good. Finally, emerge into a Keto diet for marketing - lean and powerful with documentation links bolstered by a rejuvenated marketing and docs site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bear in mind though, it&#39;s not a stroll in the park. Embrace the power of PocketHost 0.9.1, and carve your own path through the mystical dev realms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pockethost.io&quot;&gt;PocketHost&lt;/a&gt; is the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;maintenance-release&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Maintenance Release &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This release includes enhancements to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code refactoring, continuous integration, and github actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced proxy error trapping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: ga author and message&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: hoist typefest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: hoist chalk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: hoist micro-dash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: update prettierignore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: hoist pockethost JS SDK to root package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: ga&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: ga fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: ga interpolation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: better gh action messages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing - Documentation Links &amp;amp; Image Updates (#305)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: fix hard coded https protocol in frontend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: read env changes from vite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: better proxy error trapping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: fix dev startup package.json&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: prettierupdate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: package.json fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: lint formatting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: lint fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: new marketing &amp;amp; docs site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: rename pockethost.io to dashboard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: prod notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.9.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/"/>
		<updated>2023-10-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get ready to dive into the newest chapter of the PocketHost saga with the latest 0.9.0 release, offering some major enhancements that&#39;ll spring your productivity into overdrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take control with the new PocketBase JS Hooks support. All hail the &lt;code&gt;pb_hooks&lt;/code&gt; directory, a new playground for your wildest Javascript explorations. As a result, Deno worker support took the backstage, but rest assured, it&#39;s for a good reason: the stability of the sailing ship that is the PocketHost-PocketBase alliance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expect an extra layer of robustness as instances now run in Docker containers. It&#39;s a necessary security guard ensuring every instance holds its ground securely without interfering with the others. Bear with us on this one - we&#39;re expecting a little turbulence as we calibrate the Docker influence on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Witness the speed of light with Static Site Generation (SSG) on the new-look frontend, now hosted on Cloudflare Pages. It&#39;s as if the Mothership running in San Francisco engaged hyperdrive, promising almost instant load times, and delivering a huge upgrade in user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For an in-depth look at all the enhancements and discussions around v1.0 and its potential paid tiers, hop onto our dedicated Discord server. Your input might just influence the future face of PocketHost. Get your hands on the project now - this ride to fantastic, efficient web hosting is only just beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost is the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;hook-support&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Hook Support! &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost now officially supports PocketBase JS hooks via the &lt;code&gt;pb_hooks&lt;/code&gt; directory. This feature was soft-launched about a month ago and is stable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Support for Deno workers has been removed in favor of &lt;code&gt;pb_hooks&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost itself also moved some of its own code into &lt;code&gt;pb_hooks&lt;/code&gt; with mixed results: database triggers worked well, but API endpoints didn&#39;t. We hit too many library and platform incompatibilities with the goja JS runtime environment. The Deno workers allowed full nodejs compatibility, but ultimately, we felt that supporting &lt;code&gt;pb_hooks&lt;/code&gt; was going to be better for both the PocketHost and PocketBase projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;instances-now-run-in-docker&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Instances now run in Docker &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost now runs your instance in a Docker container. This helps us guarantee resources for your instance as well as secure your instance from other instances. Now that your PocketBase instance has OS-level access via &lt;code&gt;pb_hooks&lt;/code&gt;, this was a necessary security step and is good for stability too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We expect &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; temporary platform instability while we iron out any new side effects introduced by this change, but long term, the PocketHost platform will be more stable and durable with this change in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;frontend-is-now-ssg&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Frontend is now SSG &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We moved the entire frontend (built in SvelteKit) to SSG on Cloudflare Pages. This means near-instant load times for the PocketHost dashboard anywhere around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Piror to this change, the Mothership running in San Francisco USA was running a nodejs web server and serving the frontend. The user experience should be dramatically improved for everyone now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This change also gives us the added benefit of CI preview URLs for all frontend updates, even in feature branches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;v1-0-paid-tiers-roadmap-and-discussion&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;v1.0 Paid Tiers, Roadmap, and Discussion &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of these updates have surrounded discussion around an eventual v1.0 and introduction of a paid tier. There is no timeline for v1.0, but it&#39;s under active discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/channels/1128192380500193370/1153379252255862837&quot;&gt;in the v1.0 thread on our Discord server&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Already green-lit and under active development:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PocketHost dashboard feature to manage user feedback, feature suggestions, and voting on features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New marketing site and dashboard ui/ux overhaul&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charts and stats for instances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uptime monitoring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-highlights&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Other Highlights &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved logging - &lt;code&gt;console.log&lt;/code&gt; in JS hooks now appears in logs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved secrets - secrets are now passed to &lt;code&gt;pocketbase&lt;/code&gt; executable and are available in JS hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: imrpoved paid users view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: local dev setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: improve debugging mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: downloader debugging information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove old cli package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: update sftp link&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: add permalink to live publishing step&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: Cloudflare Pages SSG publishing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: SSG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: sveltekit environment variables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: invocation indexes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: comment template environment variables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: run PocketBase in debugging mode when DEBUG=true&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: gitignore update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: db migrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: secondsThisMonth in users table&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: usage tracking to JS hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: add docker-compose sample for better dx&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: mothership backup script&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: autoremove docker container at exit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: derive docker container name from instance name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: logging/debugging output&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: track uid in invocations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: user record cleanup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: update env error messages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: refactor assert()&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: support pb_hooks on monthership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove db backup constants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merge branch &#39;master&#39; of github.com:benallfree/pockethost&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: v0.9.0 update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GitBook: No commit message&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove deno worker helper lib&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: remove Deno worker, add console.log capture for pb_hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: husky linting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: formatting fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: potential paid users view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: dotenv holdover fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: startup error - initialize portmanager first&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: make ftpService await initialization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: optimize port allocation initialization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: env template typo fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: doc update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: yarn lock update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: tsx update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: prettier update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove dotenv support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: frontend tsconfig fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: dotenvify frontend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: add dotenv support to root&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: yarn.lock update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: hoist tslib and ts versions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: node version guard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: update sqlite3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: fix env.ts typing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: upgrade svelte &amp;amp; sveltekit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: hosting section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: Accept all headers in options requests (#274)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: prod logging update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: pb_hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: prevent access to pb_data and pb_migrations while instance may be running&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: pb_hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Support pb_hooks directory introduced by PocketBase 0.17.0 (#272)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: move UpdaterService&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: reactive instance subdomain in code sample section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;stats-and-info&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stats and Info &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.9.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;stars&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;424&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;userCount&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2636&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;runningInstanceCount&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;14&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;instanceCount&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3560&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;instanceCount1Hour&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;82&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;instanceCount1Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;297&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;instanceCount7Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;617&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;instanceCount30Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1159&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationCount&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2613110&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationCount1Hour&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;606&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationCount1Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15068&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationCount7Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;133707&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationCount30Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;447101&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationSeconds&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;82116629.66801019&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationSeconds1Hour&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;64166.25600000002&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationSeconds1Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;842562.3680000034&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationSeconds7Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5469632.9049999295&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;invocationSeconds30Day&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;18793014.398999963&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.8.2</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.2/"/>
		<updated>2023-07-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Witness the latest chapter of the PocketHost journey unfold with the release of version 0.8.2. This iteration, a ‘nuts and bolts’ maintenance release, focuses on ensuring your 0-to-60 transition to a live PocketBase instance—with zero-config—is smoother than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delve into the enhanced logging system, designed meticulously for in-depth debugging. Let the FTP enhancements streamline your workflow while the database migration cleanup keeps things tidy in the backend. Pointedly, don&#39;t miss the refactored &#39;Danger Zone&#39; UI— it&#39;s designed to keep you safe while still living on the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keen eyes might spot a fix for the ‘unzipper’ package failing on node v18.6.0 that was inconspicuously wreaking havoc during PocketBase version upgrades. On the same note, service templates have undergone precise recalibrations, and the &lt;code&gt;node&lt;/code&gt; version is now steadfastly locked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An array of behind-the-scene chores adds robustness while a refactored UpdaterService compliments these under-the-hood improvements. Look out for changes related to the PocketBase service and SQLite patch updates. There’s also the intro of &#39;stresser&#39; and &#39;stresser cleanup&#39; for those who love to push the boundaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The narrative of PocketHost v0.8.2 is written in its changelog. The numbers speak volumes with 359 GitHub stars, over 2000 registered users, and more than 400 instances active in the past week alone. Dive in and optimize your NodeJS experience with PocketHost 0.8.2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost is the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-s-new&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What&#39;s New &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a maintenance release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highlights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed PocketBase version upgrade stability - &lt;code&gt;unzipper&lt;/code&gt; package failing on node v18.6.0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved logging for debugging purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FTP enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database migration cleanup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactor Danger Zone UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enhancement: proxy logging output fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: logging fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: lock node version&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: unzipper nodejs incompatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: sqlite patch update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: UpdaterService&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: rename pocketbaseService&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: service template&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: stresser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: stresser cleanup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: restore pb_static in FTP service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: docs cleanup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: FTP support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: breadcrumb fluent logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: path adjustments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: maintenance mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: maintenance mode timeout fixed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;stats-and-info&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stats and Info &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;359 github stars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2000 registered users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2700 instances created&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~1.8 million instance invocations to date (# times PocketBase executable has been launched)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~400 instances active and used in the past week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.8.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.1/"/>
		<updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dive straight into PocketHost 0.8.1, the latest upheaval in your go-to &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform, set to transform backend deployment. This solution is making waves in the dev community, thanks to its ever-improving functionality and commitment to a zero-config ethos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explore a plethora of improvements in this maintenance release. Notice snappier instance launching performance, refactored Danger Zone UI, extensive logging - a debuggers dream, RPC callback fixes, corrections to documentation typos, and thorough database migration cleanups. From stressor updates to error propagation enhancements in RpcService, this release has fine-tuned the PocketHost experience, emphasizing accuracy and user convenience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, don&#39;t underestimate the impact of this update in the context of impressive growth stats. Over 2000 developers are now harnessing this tool across the development spectrum, with approximately 2700 instances created and an astounding 1.5 million instance invocations so far. With around 400 instances deemed active in the past week, there&#39;s no doubt that PocketHost 0.8.1 is not just an update but a significant gear shift for modern NodeJS developers. Therefore, probe into this platform and elevate your backend deployment game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost is the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-s-new&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What&#39;s New &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a maintenance release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highlights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved instance launching performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed typos in documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved logging for debugging purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RPC callback fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database migration cleanup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactor Danger Zone UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;wip: stressor updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix broken documentation links (#241)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merge branch &#39;master&#39; of github.com:benallfree/pockethost&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix help link in rename instance section (#240)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: async execution guard moved to common&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: instance collection constant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: collection constants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: stresser modes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: object and string logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: instance logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: ts error ignore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: port pool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merge branch &#39;live&#39;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: port pooling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(origin/live, live) enh: certbot auto-renew&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: healthyguard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: stresser instance acquisition and exclusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: instance port acquisition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: cleanup manager priority constants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;migrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: stresser exclusions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: backend service template&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: collection template&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: improve error propagation in RpcService&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: remove try/catch from rpc command responders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: improve error propgation in RpcHelper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: clean up response types for rpcs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: error messaging in safeCatch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: logger console fn update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: rpc template update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: MiniEdit error feedback and input usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: rpc callback ux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: refactor Maintenance UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: danger zone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: RpcHelper logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: watch instance logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: user log logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: secrets store &amp;amp; logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: save secrets on action&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: miniToggle call save on action&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: watchInstanceLog logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: safecatch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: stresser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;stats-and-info&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stats and Info &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;331 github stars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2000 registered users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2700 instances created&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~1.5 million instance invocations to date (# times PocketBase executable has been launched)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~400 instances active and used in the past week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.8.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/"/>
		<updated>2023-06-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dive into the new world of cloud hosting with PocketHost 0.8.0 tailored exclusively for Nodejs developers. This paradigm-shifting update revamps the already robust PocketHost by adding a plethora of new enhancements. Expect a sleeker, intuitive control panel alongside faster operations to supercharge your PocketBase deployment without batting an eye.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Midnight oil was burned redesigning the instance user interface on the dashboard, bringing you more structure and lucidity. Beware of the added &lt;em&gt;Danger Zone&lt;/em&gt;—a trapdoor leading to the potentially destructive settings for your beloved PocketBase instance. Fear not at the sight of the unknown; for the first time, instances can be renamed offering a new level of personalization to your cloud terrain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost 0.8.0 gives you the reigns of your instance with Maintenance Mode—allowing you to disengage running copies and keep them inoperational until you see fit. This proves vital during backups and restores, making them a breeze. Underneath this delightfully tidy UI and heightened control, this update hides a heart of iron. The code managing the launch and closure of instances underwent a complete overhaul, optimizing for superior stability and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, strap in, and prepare to traverse the cloud-scapes of PocketHost 0.8.0 with a heightened sense of control, crystal clarity, and  unshakable stability. Be forewarned, this journey isn’t for the faint-hearted!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost is the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-s-new&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What&#39;s New &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several MAJOR changes in this release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;new-instance-ui&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;New Instance UI &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instance UI in the dashboard has been redesigned to improve organization and clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;danger-zone&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Danger Zone &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new accordion tab, &lt;em&gt;Danger Zone&lt;/em&gt;, has been added. This tab contains potentially harmful or destructive settings for your PocketBase instance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;rename-instance&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Rename Instance &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instances can now be renamed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;instance-permalink&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Instance Permalink &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every instance is accessible from &lt;code&gt;https://&amp;lt;uuid&amp;gt;.pockethost.io&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;maintenance-mode&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Maintenance Mode &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can now put your PocketHost instance in Maintenance Mode. Maintenance mode will shut down any running copies of the instance and keep it shut down until you take it out of maintenance mode. This is helpful for backups and restores in particular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;stability-improvements&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stability Improvements &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this release, the code managing the launching and shutting down of instances has been completey reworked. The result is dramatically improved stability and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;stress-testing&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stress Testing &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each release of PocketHost is now tested with 500 simultaneous requests to hundreds of different PocketBase instances. Stress testing revealed some rare error conditions which have been corrected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: instance store and realtime responsiveness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: instance shutdown while in unhealthy state&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: frontend logger refactor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: dashbaord for large number of instances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feat: mega stability overhaul, maintenance mode, rename, respond by uuid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: version change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: process killing enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: version download enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: rpc commands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: autocancel behavior for instance client mixin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: downloadManager serialization guard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: SqliteService async serialization enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: start central pocketbase at daemon port base&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: createInvocation autocancel key&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: logging output&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: remove async promise handler pattern from InstanceLoggerService&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: FtpService logging and code formatting enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: handle preflight exceptions in tryCatch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: SqliteLogger logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove backups table from db&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove RPC commands support from db&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: remove async promise handler (won&#39;t catch errors)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: undefined value in TimerManager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: cleanupManager async cleanups and singleton shutdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: safeCatch logging and handling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: terminal colors for logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: RPC hygen templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: faq link&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: instance overview formatting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: running-&amp;gt;version&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: organize instance info in accordion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: secrets form dark mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: add admin link to instance title&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enh: bootstrap 5.3 update, hljs dark mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: remove WorkerLogFields reference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cos: tiny button refactor &amp;amp; reduce size of code copy button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: get rid of worker log fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;big: refactor instancemanager for proper shutdown when pocketbase fails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bug: reset instances on boot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bug: request hangs if pockethost doesn&#39;t launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;stats-and-info&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stats and Info &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.8.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;331 github stars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2000 registered users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2700 instances created&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~1.5 million instance invocations to date (# times PocketBase executable has been launched)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~400 instances active and used in the past week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.7.2</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.2/"/>
		<updated>2023-06-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the realm of user-friendly, zero-config platforms, PocketHost shines even brighter with its latest release, 0.7.2. Depth up the ante on your cloud solution prowess with this update that buzzes with exciting new features, including the much-anticipated ability to adjust your PocketBase version!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dive straight into the mix by experimenting with semantic versions and semantic version ranges. But don&#39;t worry about causing a retrograde mess, PocketBase has got your back! It refuses to run on an older database version, saving you from an accidental rolls back to earlier, less efficient versions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sprinkled across our change log this time, you&#39;ll find a blend of cosmetics and cleanups: CSS enhancements, backup and restore UI cleanup, to name a few. Our log context update and singleton base config are some other tweaks we&#39;re pretty chuffed about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And somewhere amidst all that code magic, we managed to clock a few personal records too. With a whopping 326 Github stars, about 2000 registered users, and over 1.5 million instance invocations to our glory, we&#39;ve got plenty reasons to celebrate. And so do you. After all, about 400 of you have kept your instances active in the past week. That&#39;s evidence of an engaged community and a tribute to the power of PocketHost. Thanks for sticking around!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost is the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-s-new&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What&#39;s New &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this release, you can now adjust the PocketBase version. It will accept semantic versions and semantic version ranges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With limited testing, it seems that PocketBase will refuse to run on an older version of the database, so there is no danger to accidentally rolling back to an earlier version of PocketBase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;change-log&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Change log &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: css cosmetics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: update pocketbase semver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: roadmap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: semver validation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: cleanup backup/restore UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove resetBackups RPC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: backup/restore cleanup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: missing WorkerLogFields type&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: log context update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: pm2 log update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: remove instance backup remanence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: singleton base config&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: add log breadcrumb support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;stats-and-info&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stats and Info &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;326 github stars (personal best!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2000 registered users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2500 instances created&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~1.5 million instance invocations to date (# times PocketBase executable has been launched)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~400 instances active and used in the past week. This tracks, about 15% of instances are in active use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.7.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.0/"/>
		<updated>2023-06-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dive headfirst into an era of streamlined development with the latest PocketHost update, version 0.7.0. Fully loaded with native PocketBase integration and a new suite of features, this update brings you the future of agile project management - turning your backend administration blueprint on its head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s the crux of what&#39;s new: from the get-go, every fresh instance you fire up will now automatically generate and run with the most recent version of PocketBase. This feature, once benched pending PocketBase&#39;s maturity, is now rolled out and ready to rumble. Trust us when we say it&#39;s game-changing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&#39;s more spice in the mix. PocketHost 0.7.0 now natively uses PocketBase migrations to manage the central database migrations of PocketHost itself. This means that every intricacy of your backend management, including maintenance mode, updates, and migrations, will be as smooth as butter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But wait, there&#39;s a bonus level! Your voice and suggestions matter. The roadmap is updated and plans are afoot to enable you, the end-user, to initiate a maintenance mode protocol for your PocketBase instance, and run migrations from your dashboard. Get ready to embrace this brave new world of seamless backend project management!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PocketHost will now always select and run the latest version of PocketBase for new instances and for the PocketHost central database. This was previously restricted until PocketBase matured more, but we think it is safe now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now using native PocketBase migrations to manage PocketHost central database migrations. Roadmap has been updated with task to allow end users to put their PocketBase instance in maintenance mode and run migrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.7.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.1/"/>
		<updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capture the upgrade in your coding adventure with the rollout of PocketHost 0.7.1, the cutting-edge update to the &#39;PocketBase in the clouds.&#39; Explore enhanced FTP accessibility, superior handling of static assets, and refined error management. Delve into essential fixes while unlocking the mysteries of an added FAQ section and transitioned docs to GitBook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost, your key to zero-config, &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform, has touched down with v0.7.0 today. The stats speak to the success, with an impressive 317 GitHub stars, almost 2000 registered users, approximately 2500 instances created, and a whopping ~ 1.5 million instance invocations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The living testament to the power of PocketHost is the tell-all FAQ section and the roadmap that keeps you updated with all the happenings in the cloud. With this release, solve FTP username link URLencoding issues, explore the terrain of routing static asset requests to the PocketBase instance, and handle http-proxy error conditions like a pro. The transition to GitBook enhances your journey while various internal error trapping and logging help to deflate potential errors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost 0.7.1 is not just an upgrade. It&#39;s your portal to elevate the quality of your technical prowess. Get into the rhythm of things, upgrade your PocketHost and let the creative coding get kicked up a notch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost, the zero-config &#39;PocketBase in the cloud&#39; platform, has reached v0.7.0 today. Thank you for everyone&#39;s continued support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/overview/faq.md&quot;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/overview/roadmap.md&quot;&gt;roadmap&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;stats&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Stats &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;317 github stars (personal best!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2000 registered users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~2500 instances created&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~1.5 million instance invocations to date (# times PocketBase executable has been launched)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~400 instances active and used in the past week. This tracks, about 15% of instances are in active use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-this-release&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;About this release &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a maintenance release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;changes&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Changes &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.7.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feature: Added FAQ section and documentation link&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: FTP username link is now properly URLencoded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: static asset requests are routed to PocketBase instance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: requests for instances not ending in &lt;code&gt;pockethost.io&lt;/code&gt; now rejected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: realtime logging API requests no longer intercepted by PocketBase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: potential timer memory leak&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: proper handling of http-proxy error conditions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chore: various internal error trapping and logging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: FTP now correctly downloads static assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: FTP now accesses &lt;code&gt;pb_migrations&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: Secrets CSS light/dark mode fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chore: remove &lt;code&gt;platform&lt;/code&gt; field from instances and backups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docs: converted to GitBook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: Increased release page limit to 100 because some old PocketBase releases were getting dropped from the github API query&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chore: adjust logfile destination on live server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chore: remove platform reference when launching instance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chore: add preflight check to tryFetch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.6.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.6.1/"/>
		<updated>2023-01-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.6.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.6.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inject a bit of swagger into your backend development with PocketHost 0.6.1. Primed, polished, and pretty darn resistant to errors - especially that tough nut semver locking error. That bugger&#39;s been swatted out into the oblivion of coding history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picture yourself steering clear of those quirky semver locking issues, navigating smoothly through your NodeJS endeavors. Imagine the delight of uninterrupted flow, with PocketHost 0.6.1 as a steadfast companion. This update might as well be the duct tape for your persistence bloopers - it&#39;s the force field that keeps the semver glitches at bay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s dig into the magic potion that makes PocketHost 0.6.1 truly extraordinary. The semver locking error, a classic stumbling block in the developer&#39;s journey, no longer poses a threat. Eradicated, deleted, fixed. That notorious error message that used to send chills down your spine? Evaporated into thin air!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So how does streamlining your web development journey sound? Fancy igniting unparalleled efficiency on your path to creating tomorrow&#39;s online innovations? Reach out and seize the day with PocketHost 0.6.1. Step into a zero-config world and let this edition turbocharge your proficiency. Trust in PocketHost to helm your creations, as we usher-in an era where open-source technologies hold the reins, making software development as seamless as a jiu-jitsu transition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed semver locking error&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.6.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.6.0/"/>
		<updated>2022-12-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.6.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.6.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behold, the fresh-off-the-coding-desk PocketHost 0.6.0! Tap into it to traverse the new frontier of FTP support. Unleash the power to streamline your workflows, uploading and managing files directly as if PocketHost was your local drive, all while savoring the same top-notch security you have come to expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn your attention to the newly minted cache support for PocketBase releases. As cool as a cucumber storing power in its cells, caching means the latest PocketBase version is always a single tap away—no more waiting for updates. Just like Neo bending the Matrix, it&#39;s time to sidestep unnecessary download times and jump straight into the action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, let&#39;s talk uptime. That elusive 99.999% target is looking closer than ever, with enhancements to instance uptime ramping up reliability. Immerse yourself in a world where your creation is readily available, keeping both you and your users smiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, put your hands together for the resolution of the CORS PUT issue. No more dealing with that pesky bug that left many scratching their heads like a glitch in the Death Star&#39;s plans. With the advent of PocketHost 0.6.0, that troublesome issue has been banished to the annals of history. Onwards and upwards, as they say!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FTP support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cache pocketbase releases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance instance uptime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CORS PUT fix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.7</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.7/"/>
		<updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.7/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.7/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prepare for a quantum leap in your development cycle, NodeJS wizards! Exiting from time&#39;s tunnel is the innovative majesty - the PocketHost version 0.5.7, punctually delivered on 26th December 2022. This upgrade isn’t just Christmas-gift-wrapped graham crackers, it redefines game rules!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This update not only rectifies a constellation of lurking production errors but also transcends them into the realm of the forgotten past. Bid goodbye to unattended issues and invite a future of seamless code execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Confidently harness the power of PATCH and DELETE CORS operations, now an integral part of PocketHost&#39;s capabilities. No stone left unturned, no HTTP method left unsupported, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, be stoked about the addition of PM2 production support, a sturdy engine to propel your applications into the land of user delight. Excellent, for applications that need to survive application crashes and unexpected system reboots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the cherry on the top of this node.js sundae - an inventive &#39;auto-upgrade&#39; feature with SemVer tagging. It&#39;s &amp;quot;The One With SemVer Tagging&amp;quot;, promising a curve of continuous improvement rather than erratic jumps. The kind of predictability software developers (and Ross Geller) would appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix various production errors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support PATCH and DELETE CORS operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add pm2 production support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement auto-upgrade feature and semver tagging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.6</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.6/"/>
		<updated>2022-12-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.6/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.6/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;title: Salutations from PocketHost 0.5.6!
date: 2022-12-24T00:00:00.000Z
description: Unveiling PocketHost 0.5.6, a game-changing episode coming in hot, parting ways with Docker and tying up with PocketBase 0.10.4. Custom-built for all the NodeJS maestros out there, the latest take aims at delivering efficiency and stability. A commitment to streamline your programming sail and free you from hitch, so you can anchor all your focus where it truly belongs – your masterpiece.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unravel PocketHost&#39;s latest update which turns the tables effectively. Docker gets a courteous bow out, making room for bigger and better. Now, you dive straight into the core, fine-tuning your projects with increased proficiency and zero distractions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Embrace the new and upgraded PocketBase 0.10.4. This version offers you unmatched compatibility across all your NodeJS endeavors. It&#39;s all-inclusive, reliable, and designed to line-up your coding experience - efficient and carefree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider this as a redefined commitment from PocketHost - a promise to keep your coding streamlined, no distractions, only creativity. Your creations are the stars here; PocketHost 0.5.6 is just the robust rocket fuel propelling them to the skies. So, get ready to celebrate more freedom and fewer hiccups; the new era of NodeJs programming has begun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, it&#39;s the dawning of a new age in the realms of PocketHost and you&#39;re in for a whirl. This step forward is sure to change the game. Buckle up, developers, it&#39;s about to get exciting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PocketBase 0.10.4 update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.5</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.5/"/>
		<updated>2022-12-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.5/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.5/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buckle up, fellow coders, PocketHost has propelled into new frontiers with its latest software upgrade to version 0.5.5! In this update, we’re granting seamless integration with the freshest editions of PocketBase; namely version 0.9.2, 0.10.0, and 0.10.1. With this exciting evolution of PocketHost, expanding the findings in your codeverse just went from Warp to Ludicrous Speed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our new 0.5.5 edition of PocketHost handles all your behind-the-scenes tasks, so you can laser focus on crafting superb applications. We spin up instances of PocketBase - with versions 0.9.2, 0.10.0, and 0.10.1 - quicker than you can unravel a Rubik’s cube. It&#39;s like having Q from James Bond in your corner, crafting all the DevOps and Linux gadgetry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this upgrade, PocketHost has leveled up to become your ultimate ally in web development. Each instance of PocketBase is dedicatedly engineered to put efficiency and convenience at the helm of all your operations, serving as your ride-or-die companion in your coding conquests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So embrace the power of PocketHost to whip up next-level creations and conquer the galaxy of enterprise-grade applications, faster than a speed-dating algorithm at a Hackathon! Make peace, too, with those DevOps tasks that are about as approachable as a box of Schrodinger’s cats. Welcome to a whole new dimension of deployment. Confidence level: Tony Stark on espresso.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, venture forth and boldly code where no dev has coded before. With PocketHost 0.5.5, the code-verse is your oyster!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: PocketBase 0.9.2 update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: PocketBase 0.10.0, 0.10.1 updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.4</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.4/"/>
		<updated>2022-12-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.4/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.4/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buckle up and swiftly ride into the latest offerings from sunny PocketHost 0.5.4. Dive into the matrix as we unravel essential adjustments, bug fixes, and crucial backend compatibility upgrades. It&#39;s a wild journey on this Most Serene Republic of Javascript, and no doubt - every glitch de-bugged makes it even more amazing to traverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, transcend that baffling issue where the &#39;Create Instance&#39; cancel button decided to go MIA. In this version, the cancel button has been tamed and will obediently revert operations upon command. Confusing encounter while trying to cancel? Not on our watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, ghosts in the machine leaving your instances inactive for real-time events have been banished. Say farewell to instances hitting the snooze button. Brace yourself for instantaneous reactions, as keeping up with real-time events is now a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, cue the drumrolls for back-end compatibility upgrades. Seamless support for PocketBase 0.9.0 and 0.9.1 has been meticulously architected. Now, you can straddle comfortably between these versions, without breaking a sweat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, PocketHost 0.5.4 is an engaging ride onwards and upwards, taking us a step closer to an even more splendid user experience. Plug in the code, grab some coffee, and watch the magic unfurl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: Create Instance cancel button does not work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: instances do not stay active for realtime events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: support for PocketBase 0.9.0 and 0.9.1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.3</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.3/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.3/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.3/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brace yourselves for the sweet sting of progress as PocketHost 0.5.3 lands with gusto. Peep under the hood and you&#39;ll find a backend revamp geared for the future, built on the might of go 1.19.3. From polishing the dashboard details to fortifying the backup functionalities, this version comes ready to rock the stage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bid farewell to unhelpful, blank-stare inducing error messages. PocketHost 0.5.3 has been infused with an oracle-like ability to articulate clearly about backup discrepancies. Now, encountering a failed backup due to a non-existent instance won&#39;t feel like deciphering an alien language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experience the sheer joy of asynchronous operations streamlined for better performance and neat, courteous contextual logging. The version number has moved on like a nomad, finding a new home in the base package.json. Just when you thought auto-cancellation might have taken a sabbatical, guess what, it&#39;s back and hustling!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The backup feature in PocketHost has historically been more protective than a mother in a Kung Fu film. With 0.5.3, it now reinforces the defense by outright denying backups for missing data directories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essentially, it&#39;s not just a new iteration - it&#39;s a whole new animal. So, buckle up, code ninjas, and enjoy this smooth new ride in the world of PocketHost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: incorrect instance information displaying on dashboard details in some cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: more helpful error message when backup fails for nonexistent instance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: move version number to base package.json&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor: logging and async helpers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: restore auto-cancellation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: rebuild with go 1.19.3 and include in bin name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: Disallow backups if data dir doesn&#39;t exist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.2</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.2/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;title: PocketHost 0.5.2: Explore Your Expansive NodeHorizon
date: 2022-11-19T00:00:00.000Z
description: Scale new heights with the latest evolution of PocketHost v0.5.2. The stalwart backend service explicitly crafted for the NodeJS developer that dares to step beyond the ordinary. See what&#39;s within the Pandora&#39;s box of rc3, rc4, and 0.8.0-final support. Delve into yarn optimization with deduplication, unravel enhanced TypeScript bootstrapping, and tackle the account verification fix that packs a punch with a hard-redirect. Ready for the journey? Let&#39;s hit the road with PocketHost - your one-stop solution to seamless deployments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kicking off with the heavy-duty stuff, PocketHost v0.5.2 now embraces support for rc3, rc4, and 0.8.0-final. A powerful combo sure to satisfy even the most ambitious coders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, let&#39;s talk optimisation. Yarn&#39;s reputation as a quick and secure dependency manager goes hand in hand with PocketHost&#39;s ethos. By introducing deduplication in this release, PocketHost has achieved the hitherto elusive feat of a leaner, more efficient build pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Typescript&#39;s static type-checking capacity adds a layer of reliability that JavaScript can&#39;t provide. Enhancing TypeScript bootstrapping, therefore, brings you the power of early error-detection while keeping improvements manageable between versions, ensuring faster, more efficient deployments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, the cherry on top - unraveling a longstanding fix. The account verification process now incorporates a hard-redirect, curing any associated validation hiccups. Be bulletproof, be trustworthy. Let the PocketHost 0.5.2 update make deployments a cinch, freeing you to focus on what truly matters - creating outstanding applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: rc3, rc4, 0.8.0-final support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: dedupe yarn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix: Account verification needs to hard-redirect&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore: improved bootstrap TS support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.1/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Title: Unveiling PocketHost 0.5.1
Date: 2022-11-16T00:00:00.000Z
Description: &amp;quot;Embrace the evolutionary improvements of PocketHost 0.5.1. This update zaps the annoying bug which spawned a 404 error post-instance creation, rendering it obsolete. More so, let&#39;s not forget the rectified issue with the SQLite3 build. PocketHost steadily and passionately paves the way to the podium of go-to backend solutions for the NodeJS developer community.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PocketHost 0.5.1, the latest iteration, cleans up its act by fixing two key issues that have bugged developers. The pesky problem of 404 error occurring right after creating an instance? Consider it history. The bugs didn&#39;t stand a chance against the tech surgeons behind PocketHost, dedicated to enabling uninterrupted backend operations for all web developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SQLIte3 build gets a much-needed fix in this update as well. Do you remember those frustrating moments due to SQLite3 glitches? Worry no more. This update is the remedy for the SQLite3 hangover, making your journey with PocketHost more satisfying and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With PocketHost&#39;s devotion to perfection and resolve to be your first choice for backend solutions, this update signifies their unwavering commitment. Consider this a step further on our never-ending quest toward backend nirvana. Step into this new realm of seamless backend operations with PocketHost 0.5.1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: 404 after creating instance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: SQLite3 build&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.5.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.0/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.5.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charge into the nexus of backend development with PocketHost 0.5.0! Bearing an armory of new features, it elevates your backend game to a new level. Like a Time Lord with backups, tap into the ability to create data backups. Never lose sight of your version with the version display feature implanted right next to the PocketHost logo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experience a wave of user interface refreshments. Enjoy an enhanced account activation process—a seamless experience reminiscent of a console&#39;s perfectly executed command. Further, forget fretting over forgotten passwords, as the password reset feature is here for your rescue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Navigate with ease through an updated menu—may your journey be as smooth as a high-performing algorithm. The pièce de résistance is that your PocketBase instance version number is now displayed on the dashboard, a cue taken from your own coding principles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With 0.5.0, PocketHost is staking its claim as more than just a backend hosting and deployment service. It&#39;s a doyen of developer tools ready to assist, inspire, and improve your code crafting process much like a faithful judo partner, always there to support yet ever challenging you to be better. It&#39;s time to fire up your terminals and experiment with the new gadgets in your tech arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create data backups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display version near PocketHost logo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Account activation ux enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Password reset feature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Menu ux refresh&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PocketBase instance version number now shows on dashboard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.4.2</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.2/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;title: Explore the New Frontier with PocketHost 0.4.2!
date: 2022-11-05T00:00:00.000Z
description: A game-changer is here in the realm of backend development with PocketHost’s latest 0.4.2 update. Enter a higher dimension of project tracking and resource management with real-time runtime metrics that display your instance usage in minutes per month. Ride the wave of efficiency and potentiate your project performance with this dynamic new feature!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unleash the full potential of your PocketHost instance, and let the numbers do the talking. With the 0.4.2 update, tap into an insightful dashboard that presents real-time runtime metrics offering by-the-minute insights on the usage of your PocketHost instance. Should you desire to render Time Lords redundant, imagine the immense power to manage and architect your ongoing and future projects, knowing exactly how many minutes per month your instances sail in the digital sea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Less guesswork, more precision. Decode your projects’ performance with laser-sharp clarity, and take optimisation to never-before-seen levels. It&#39;s like gaining a mystical sixth sense for grasping the nuances of your backend developmental processes. Go ahead, give the 0.4.2 update a try and make backend development more of a strategic chess game than a showy firework display.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring it on future, we&#39;re armed with facts and stats – PocketHost’s latest 0.4.2 update. The next round of the node.js symphony is here for all you cloud orchestra directors out there. Amplify the rhythm of your backend development projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Runtime metrics now show how many minutes per month an instance has used&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.4.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.1/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entering the arena with a mighty roar, it&#39;s PocketHost 0.4.1 - primed and ready to unleash a wave of enhancements that will drive your node.js creations straight into the heart of the digital world. With support now extended across 0.7.10 and 0.8.0-rc2, this upgrade is standing on the shoulders of the coding giants, beckoning you to follow suit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peel back the curtains and you&#39;ll find the engine-room of PocketHost 0.4.1 is now fuelled by go 1.19.3. This latest iteration of the open source programming language designed for efficiency and reliability is powering up PocketHost, making it an even more formidable force in the cloud hosting space. Brace yourselves for an invigorating sprint filled with streamlined performance and precision that can put a Swiss watch to shame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dig a little deeper and the Docker build system will catch your attention, shuffling on its dancing shoes and spinning a whole new set of updated moves. The improvements to the Docker build system are like adding an extra gear to your interstellar hyperdrive. So, sit tight as PocketHost 0.4.1 takes you on a wild ride across the ever-growing landscape of cloud tech, letting you focus on what you love most - creating stuff that makes a difference. Let&#39;s take the leap together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for 0.7.10 and 0.8.0-rc2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update to go 1.19.3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker build system updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.4.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.0/"/>
		<updated>2022-11-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.4.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a seat, nod to the screen and prepare to dive into the world of PocketHost 0.4.0. Unveiling an update that is ripe with enhancements tailored to bolster your project workflows. This fresh layer of technology comes loaded with complete support for PocketBase 0.8 – propelling you closer to that 100% proficiency mark in backend solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entering stage right, we witness the introduction of the ingenious, &#39;platforms&#39;, a concept designed for seamless version control. An invaluable ally for NodeJS developers as they traverse the path of project streamlining. In the fickle world of version control, &#39;platforms&#39; stand as the Han Solo to your Millennium Falcon, navigating the intricate passages within the abyss of coding with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rise, pocket that coffee-filled mug and embrace the robust infrastructure offered by pockethost.io’s latest update. Remember, progress in coding isn&#39;t measured by the sweat on your brow, but the smoothness and fluidity of your workflow. Step towards that coding nirvana by wielding this serendipitous update to your arsenal. Unleash the power of PocketHost 0.4.0 and make the coding galaxy your sandbox. No need to hold your breath, the force will always be with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PocketBase 0.8 support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduced &amp;quot;platforms&amp;quot; concept for version control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>awesome-pockebase has 20+ community resources and growing</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/awesome-pocketbase-20-and-growing/"/>
		<updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/awesome-pocketbase-20-and-growing/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/awesome-pocketbase-20-and-growing/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dive into the expansive universe of PocketBase on GitHub, courtesy of the meticulously curated https://github.com/benallfree/awesome-pocketbase. It&#39;s your immediate gateway to a galaxy that now boasts over 20 vibrant community resources and counting. Python SDK may have been the latest pioneer, but it&#39;s one of a rather intriguing line-up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explore the terrain that includes everything from starter kits to demo apps, samples tailored to distinct languages and frameworks, a toolbox of SQLite resources, and much more. But it doesn&#39;t end there! If you have been tinkering away, creating a project for PocketBase, then it&#39;s time for you to step into the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure to establish a connection and get listed. There&#39;s a thriving community of fellow explorers eagerly awaiting the chance to draw on your PocketBase project. Get involved, share your work, and be part of this flourishing ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&#39;t just concede to the magic of PocketBase. Amplify it! Raise your voice, showcase your project, and help librate the full potential of PocketBase with your contributions. This is your call to action. Connect, create, and conquer. Let&#39;s make PocketBase even more awesome than it already is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I maintain https://github.com/benallfree/awesome-pocketbase. We have over 20 community resources (Python SDK is the latest addition). The resources include starter kits, demo apps, language- and framework-specific samples, SQLite tools, and more. Check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are the maintainer of a project for PocketBase, please connect with me to get listed.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.3.2</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.2/"/>
		<updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.2/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;title: Unleashing PocketHost 0.3.2: A NodeJS Developer&#39;s New Best Friend
date: 2022-10-26T00:00:00.000Z
description: With PocketHost version 0.3.2, step into the empowering realm of amplified efficiency and bolstered security. Unearth the might of PBScript — now in a spruced up repository that champions ease of access. Raising the security bar a notch higher, accounts are now mandated to undergo verification before getting the green signal to operate an instance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Embark on a transformative journey towards enhanced accessibility with the newly migrated PBScript repository. No more hide and seek to find it. Simple, straightforward, just the way a NodeJS wrangler prefers it. With this move, tap into the repository with fewer clicks and more success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Security slid into our spotlight and decided to take center stage. PocketHost 0.3.2 is a fortress that only permits entrance after stringent account verification. Run an instance? Not until we know you&#39;re legit. This safety-first mantra of being &#39;verified before you&#39;re amplified&#39; boosts security while fostering an environment that respects authenticity and protects your creative NodeJS endeavors. Exploit this pivotal notch-up and make your server-side applications impervious to malware henchmen, as you play the melody of efficient coding on the powerful strings of PocketHost. The force is with you, node-wranglers. Craft your masterpiece with PocketHost 0.3.2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Migrated PBScript repository to here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accounts must now be verified before running an instance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.3.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.1/"/>
		<updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strap in, coder jockeys, let&#39;s blast off into the refreshing depths of PocketHost 0.3.1, rolled out this October, full throttle with features that will have your fingers itching to hit those keys. Eager to increase your project visibility across browsers? Make your mark with OpenGraph support, a game changer for managing how URLs display in social media. Expect more traffic, higher engagement, and a significantly enhanced user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, let&#39;s switch gears to the most requested feature - enhanced dark mode. Coding late into the night? Save those retinas without compromising code quality, because now you can. Imagine pairing up with Darth Vader for a coffee catch-up in The Matrix. Sounds intense? That’s what we’re dishing up. The updated dark mode offers improved readability, reducing eye strain during those all-night coding marathons. It’s clean, focused and makes those long coding sessions a joy rather than a chore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So next time you find yourself cursing under your breath at a stubborn piece of code late into the night, remember – PocketHost&#39;s got your six. OpenGraph and Dark Mode support are here to make your life easier and your users&#39; experience better. Emerge victorious from those late-night battles with code; victorious and a little less strained. Happy coding!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenGraph support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Darkmode enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.3.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.0/"/>
		<updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.3.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unveil the raw power of PocketHost 0.3.0! This game-changing upgrade has shifted the gears with amplified Docker and proxy support, expanded developer documentation, and a total UX overhaul. Now, you have the capacity to operate varying versions of PocketBase for bespoke scenarios, including beta/dev, decked with an eye-catching running status display in vibrant green.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dive into the enhanced realtime support in the proxy, flawlessly turning around the shortcomings of the previous versions. The developer docs have been overhauled to encompass more comprehensive instructions and hands-on examples, shunning any unclear notions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experience Docker functioning at its superlative for both dev and production environments, as Docker support has received a significant improvement. Navigate through a completely redesigned user interface, engineered with simplicity and usability at its core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep track of your PocketBase instance status with ease, as idle/running statuses now project in an unmissable shade of green. Push the envelope even further by spawning different versions of PocketBase per instance tailored to fit your custom use-cases, including beta/dev. With PocketHost 0.3.0, tapping into the immense potential of backend development has never been smoother or more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved realtime support in proxy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated developer docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved Docker support for dev and prod&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete UX redesign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Idle/running status for PB instance now shows in green&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to run separate versions of PocketBase per instance for custom cases including beta/dev&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.2.0</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.2.0/"/>
		<updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.2.0/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.2.0/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immerse yourself in the expansive world of PocketHost 0.2.0, the latest iteration of this user-friendly, fully-managed PocketBase hosting service. Rejoice in the full Dockerization of services for seamless project execution while basking in the glow of substantial, dynamic proxy-driven scaling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Say goodbye to constant crashes due to memory constraints, as the dynamic proxy in v0.2.0 introduces just-in-time launching of your PocketBase instances. The period of inactivity now triggers the shutdown of an instance until the next request, ensuring cost-effective usage and optimal performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think power. Picture an upgraded server delivering 4GB RAM and dual CPUs, thus creating abundant room for your creative indulgence. Imagine the potential with an upcoming fly.io integration, allowing on-demand spinning up of instances, leaving behind the era of shared tenancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, envision the convenience of an instant backend, complete with email and S3, brought to you by shared tenancy on pockethost.io. Imagine the synergistic power of the forthcoming PBScript release combined with pockethost integration for an unrivaled BaaS experience. Finally, expect a refreshed SvelteKit UI for pockethost, courtesy of @brewhousedigital, promising an aesthetic overhaul soon. To join the rocket ride of this evolution, explore https://github.com/benallfree/pockethost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fully managed PocketBase hosting service https://pockethost.io has been updated to v0.2.0. Go check it out and spin up your very own PocketBase instance 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This release is &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/benallfree/pockethost/blob/master/docker/docker-compose.yaml&quot;&gt;fully Dockerized&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;v0.2.0 scales much better than v0.0.1 by using a &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/benallfree/pockethost/blob/master/packages/daemon/src/ProxyServer.ts#L40&quot;&gt;dynamic proxy approach&lt;/a&gt;. In the previous version, PocketBase instances stayed running and eventually crashed 🔥 the server due to memory constraints. In this version, the proxy launches your PocketBase instance just-in-time when a request comes in. After a period of inactivity, your PocketBase instance will be &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/benallfree/pockethost/blob/master/packages/daemon/src/InstanceManager.ts#L148&quot;&gt;shut down until a new request comes in&lt;/a&gt;. The &amp;quot;first hit&amp;quot; cost of launching your PocketBase instance from a cold start seems to take &amp;lt;500ms, so it&#39;s almost not noticeable under normal application use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also upgraded the server to 4GB RAM and 2 CPUs, so there should be plenty of room to play around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At some point down the road, we may accept fly.io machine keys and use fly.io&#39;s &amp;quot;machine proxy&amp;quot; service to spin up your instances on-demand. At that point, there won&#39;t be shared tenancy anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I think shared tenancy does have a place in this space. There is something very nice and easy about logging in to pockethost.io and having an instantly configured backend including email and S3, and maybe some day Litestream too. That combined with the upcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/benallfree/pbscript&quot;&gt;PBScript&lt;/a&gt; release and pockethost integration gives you a powerful BaaS without ever going near servers, re-compiling anything, deploying architecture-specific binaries, or needing to manage hosting provider API keys. You literally just get a pockethost URL like &lt;a href=&quot;https://harvest.pockethost.io/_&quot;&gt;https://harvest.pockethost.io/_&lt;/a&gt;, feed it to your client SDK, and go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;@brewhousedigital generously offered to take a look at the SvelteKit UI for pockethost and might spruce it up a bit. My design skills are lacking and I&#39;m very aware 🙈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contributions and discussion for this project at https://github.com/benallfree/pockethost&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>PocketHost 0.0.1</title>
		<link href="https://pockethost.io/blog/0.0.1/"/>
		<updated>2022-09-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://pockethost.io/blog/0.0.1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://pockethost.io/blog/0.0.1/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unleash the alpha magic of PocketHost 0.0.1, an inventive, one-click solution that will transform how you host PocketBase projects. Let your creative web development juices flow as &lt;a href=&quot;https://pockethost.io&quot;&gt;pockethost.io&lt;/a&gt;, our groundbreaking product, offers compact multi-tenant hosting handled by a single Digital Ocean VPS and a whip-smart Svelte front-end. No need to tackle SSL certification and dynamic port assignment - they’re instant and automatic here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marvel at how this lean, mean hosting machine operates. With pockethost.io, a keenly focused daemon runs on your VPS, always alert for new records from the primary pocketbase instance. Spotting one, it springs into action, provisioning an SSL cert, updating nginx, creating the data storage location, then locating a free port to give life to a new pocketbase instance solely committed to the new entry. Fear no crashes, everything automatically resurrects during startup. Keep a watchful eye on instance health, uptime, port number and more with an admin-only table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rejoice, as each pocketbase instance claims its own subdomain. PocketHost 0.0.1 is still evolving. Future releases will offer even more, such as the ability to preconfigure pocketbase instances and more dynamic email configurations. Your feedback and suggestions will help drive which direction we head next. Edison once said, &amp;quot;I find out what the world needs, then I proceed to invent it.&amp;quot; Let&#39;s invent together. Join the journey now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have an alpha up at https://pockethost.io.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Running on a single Digital Ocean VPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontend is Svelte plus a pocketbase backend (the mothership)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VPS has a daemon running that listens to new records from the main pocketbase instance. When it finds a new record, it provisions an SSL cert, updates nginx, creates a data storage location, finds a free port, and spawns a new pocketbase instance dedicated to the new entry. If anything ever crashes, this daemon will re-spawn all pocketbase instances at startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I keep an internal table (admin only) of instance info including health, uptime, port number, and other goodies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each pocketbase instance gets its own subdomain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still to do:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there a way to preconfigure the pocketbase instance with the correct Application URL?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there a way to preconfigure the instance with a &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;subdomain&amp;gt;@pockethost.io&lt;/code&gt; email address? I have Amazon SES approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It might make sense to shut down idle instances after 7 days or something. Waiting for a problem first.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still interested in a multitenant scenario where a single pocketbase instance can handle requests based on an &lt;code&gt;X-PocketBase-Tenant&lt;/code&gt; header or something&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;@ganigeorgiev Let me know what you think. Also, if the PocketHost name is too close to PocketBase please tell me and I&#39;ll change it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
